realdatajobs.com 2014-02-09

# Real data jobs | Online jobs , Part time jobs , Home based Jobs , online data jobs , Translation work

We at Glow ADS are committed to safeguarding and protecting the personal information that we collect and receive during our normal course of business transactions. This may also include information received by us through your previous and past transactions or even from your visit to this site.

This privacy policy provides details on what happens to your personal information that you may provide to this website.

Please read the following privacy policy carefully to learn about how your privacy is a matter of great importance to us at Glow ADS. This privacy policy is updated frequently, so you are requested to review the policy from time to time to apprise yourself of the latest version.

**Data integrity**

Glow ADS collects personal information only for the specific purpose that it is intended for and in total compliance to this privacy policy or any other applicable confidentiality, security agreement relating to the protection of sensitive personal information.

**Personal Information**

Personal information includes information that is personally identifiable and those which are otherwise are not publicly available. Such personal information may include but are not limited to, your name, mailing address, telephone number or contact details, age, sex, email id, bank details, etc.

When you register as a member, you create an account with Glow ADS for which we may ask you for some personal information. This may include your email id and password to provide you with access to our website services and at the same time prevent misuse through the unauthorised access of your account.

**Handling and storing**

At Glow ADS we take utmost care in protecting and safeguarding all your personal information at all times. The employees of Glow ADS who will be given access to personal information database of the members will be under a confidentiality agreement which is designed and implemented for the protection of your personal information. There are strict restrictions enforced with regard to access to personal information by employees, members, affiliates and agents of Glow ADS. Such of those who are provided with the access to such personal information for the purpose of operation, developing or improving the services are bound by confidentiality obligations. Non-conformance to such obligations would give rise to appropriate disciplinary action including suspension and termination apart from legal action based on the gravity of the situation.

At Glow ADS we take all appropriate security measures to protect your personal information against unauthorised access, retrieval and use of such information for further dissemination. We also ensure that there is no unauthorised alteration, destruction or disclosure of your personal information by periodically reviewing the data security measures that we have implemented. Such measures may include the review process of data collection, processing, storage, including physical security measures that are designed to enhance the security of personal information.

During the course of our business transactions and the operation of our website, we may need to handle, transfer and store your personal information at a location outside that of our web server. As a member, by providing your data, you agree to this transfer and storing of your personal information at a location outside that of Glow ADS. We at Glow ADS are committed to treat your personal information with utmost care to ensure that your data is transferred and stored safely and securely.

The sending of data over the Internet is prone to being intercepted and is not considered totally secure. We at Glow ADS do not guarantee security of such data sent electronically by you over the Internet. You agree to send such data entirely at your own risk.

**Sharing of Personal Information**

At Glow ADS we shall refrain from sharing your personal information to any third party apart from during the below detailed situations:
  1. Where such information is made necessary to be shared as mandated by legal obligations and other law enforcements.
  2. During the due process of business transactions your personal information may require sharing with our trusted affiliates, partners or agencies. During such sharing of personal information, we mandate that the third party agency handling such information is in compliance with our privacy policy apart from other confidentiality measures.
  3. In the event of Glow ADS selling or divesting part or whole of its business to a buyer who may gain title to the business, Glow ADS would notify its members before the transfer of such data to the third party.
  4. As a measure to strengthen security of personal information Glow ADS may be required to share personal information to third party agencies for enhancing security methods or for reducing risk of fraud.

**Third party links**

The website of Glow ADS may include links to many third parties such as affiliates, partners, agencies or advertisements. The presence of such links on the website of Glow ADS does not necessarily mean that Glow ADS endorses the privacy policy of that third party site. You are requested to review the privacy policy of that third party site before sharing or providing them with your personal information.

**Access to your personal information**

As a member you are entitled to request for access to your personal information that we have in our database. However, you will be charged an appropriate fee to cover the administration costs, if any incurred by Glow ADS in providing you with such data.

As a member with Glow ADS you can update your personal information available with us at any time. In the event of you choosing to terminate the membership with Glow ADS, all your personal information including your profile and messages in your inbox of the account you hold with us will be removed from our servers. Due to the server configuration, such deletion of profile may not necessarily mean that your data is deleted immediately. There may be certain back up files and residual copies that will remain on the server for a period of time before being permanently deleted.

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are meant to provide information about the general use of the computer and of the Internet. These cookies are downloaded and stored on to your computer’s hard drive disk while you visit websites. While these cookies do not provide personal information, they provide statistical data which may provide information on your general use of the Internet.

At Glow ADS we may use the cookies wherever we find it appropriate solely for the purpose of improving the services of our website. However, advertisers and affiliates on our website may also use such cookies which are downloaded to your computer once you click the ads appearing on our website. We have no control over the use of cookies by our advertisers and affiliates.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

In a bid to enhance the confidentiality and data security measures of your personal information, this privacy policy may get updated from time to time. You are therefore requested to visit this section of our website periodically to get the most updated version of our privacy policy.

**Feedback and contacting us**

In case you need any further details regarding privacy policy apart from what is provided here, you are free to contact us through email that we have furnished in the contact us section of our website.
